pinerly.com 2015-09-07

# Reachli :: Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

Reachli recognizes the importance of protecting the personal information that it holds. On this page you'll learn that you own and control what you share so that we make your experience perfect. We do ask you to treat our service and community with respect and if you stumble across anything that looks inappropriate, to please let us know.

This Privacy Policy explains how information about you is collected, used and disclosed by Reachli Services (when you use our websites, mobile applications and other online products and services collectively, the "Services"), which are operated and managed by Pinerly, Inc. a Delaware corporation.

We may change this Privacy Policy to improve our Services and as we make changes, we will notify you by revising the date at the top of the policy and, in some cases, we may provide you with additional notice (such as adding a statement to our websites' homepages or sending you a notification). We encourage you to read these updates to understand our information practices and the ways to protect your privacy.

Defined Terms. Several of the important terms used in this Privacy Policy, including "Member", "Reachli", "Reachli Services", "Reachli Site", are defined in Reachli's "General Terms of Use".

**Collection of Information**

Reachli only collects personal information by lawful means, and only that which is reasonably necessary for the stated purposes of using the Services. In almost all cases, and whenever possible, we collect personal information about you from you. For example your username, password, email address, phone number, and age. These are used to create your Reachli account, use the Services to send or receive a message, add remove or block other contacts on the Service, request customer support or otherwise communicate with us regarding Reachli and our Services.

**How We Use and Collect the Information**

When a Visitor uses the Reachli Services, we automatically recognize their IP address, device type, hardware model, operating system, operating system version, unique device identifier, access time, pages viewed, referrer, and language set. We use cookies to store visitors preferences, record session information, record user-specific information when to provide a better service when Visitors return to Reachli, customizing content to ensure all is understood when doing anything on Reachli.

Reachli may use personal information to: provide access to the Reachli Site and Reachli Services; manage and develop Reachli's business and operations; learn about the needs of current and potential Members; develop or offer services and products tailored to these needs and communicate with these clients regarding current and future Services; respond to and follow up on Visitor and Member inquiries, comments and suggestions; address financial matters including billing and record-keeping for audit and account collection purposes; and report illegal, unethical or other serious and unacceptable misconduct on the part of Members.

With your consent, we may collect information about the location of your device and access your device's native phonebook and image storage applications. These will help facilitate your use of certain features of the Reachli Services such as, but not limited to, matching and adding contacts from your phonebook, using photos or videos in your camera roll photos to create and send new messages, and store created messages.

**Use of "Cookies"** : A "cookie" is a small data file that can be placed on the hard drive of a person who visits a Website such as the Reachli Site. Reachli may use cookies to collect, store, and track information for statistical purposes to improve the Reachli Services and to manage our networks. If you are a Member, we will use a cookie to save your settings and provide customizable and personalized services. These cookies do not enable third parties to access any of your Member information. Additionally, be aware that if you visit websites that are linked to the Reachli Site, you may be required to accept cookies. Non-affiliated partners or sponsors may also use cookies. Reachli does not control use of these cookies and expressly disclaims responsibility for information collected through them.

**Analytics Services Provided by Others:** On the Reachli Services, as with most other commercial Services, we may monitor traffic patterns, site usage and related site information in order to optimize our web service. We may allow others to provide analytics services on our behalf. These entities may use cookies, web beacons and other technologies to collect information about your use of the Services and other websites, including your IP address, web browser, pages viewed, time spent on pages, links clicked and conversion information. This information may be used to, among other things, analyze and track data, determine the popularity of certain content and better understand your online activity. With vendors, consultants and other service providers who need access to such information to carry out work on our behalf

**Sharing of Information**

**Disclosure of Personal Information** : Under normal circumstances, Reachli will only disclose personal information for purposes related to the provision of one or more Reachli Services to a Member, or with the express consent of such Member, or if required or authorized by law.

In connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company, the prospective purchaser would normally conduct a "due diligence" review of Reachli's records. This could involve a review of Reachli's data, including personal information. Any such review would be subject to strict confidentiality provisions and would not permit the recording or removal of any personal information.

**Consent to Collection, Use and Disclosure:** We may obtain a person's consent to the collection, use and disclosure of his or her information either expressly, for stated purposes (such as in a Membership application or a request for information about the Reachli Site and Reachli Services), or implicitly, such as when the purposes are indicated by the relevant circumstances. Any such consent may be withdrawn or amended by contacting Reachli's privacy staff ([privacy@reachli.com](mailto:privacy@reachli.com)) and subject to any legal or contractual restrictions and upon reasonable notice to Reachli. For example, if a person tells us that he or she no longer wishes to receive information about the Reachli Site and Reachli Reachli, we will comply with said request.

A person's consent to Reachli's collection of certain personal information may be required for Reachli to provide the Reachli Site and Reachli Services. However, Reachli will not require, as a condition of providing access to the Reachli Site or Reachli Services, that any personal information unrelated to Reachli be collected.

**Voluntary Member Surveys** : We may conduct both business and individual Member surveys. We encourage Members to participate in these surveys as they provide us with information that enables us to improve Reachli Services and how we provide them to you. Your personal information and responses will remain strictly confidential even if the survey is conducted by a third party. Participation in our Member surveys is always voluntary.

**Special Cases** : In exceptional circumstances, Reachli may disclose personal information about Visitors or Members, or information regarding your use of the Reachli Services or Reachli Site, if, in our sole discretion, we believe that it is reasonable to do so, including: to obey laws, regulations, or governmental or legal requests for such information; to disclose information that is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our Terms of Use or other policies; to operate the Reachli Services properly; or to protect Reachli and our Members.

**Access to Personal Information:** We will respond promptly to any request for access to your personal information. There will be no cost for reasonable requests to such access, unless you request copies of records or your request involves significant retrieval costs. We will advise you of the cost, if any, prior to retrieving such records or information. Reachli will not respond to requests for access to personal information that are frivolous, vexatious or repetitious.

In certain circumstances, we may be unable to provide access to some or all of the personal information that we hold about you. Such circumstances include those in which the personal information cannot be separated from the records of others, or cannot be disclosed for reasons of personal security or commercial confidentiality.

**No Privacy Here:** Member acknowledges that in general, other than private messages sent between Members and personal information provided to Reachli to set up a Reachli account, all public messages and other information and communications submitted or posted by a Member to any part of the Reachli Site (collectively, "Communications"), presently or in the future, such as the public feed, message boards, discussion groups, blogs and other communications facilities available to Members (collectively, "Communities"), are public and not private Communications, and that others may access and read such Communications without the knowledge or consent of Member. If any of the Communities permits the submission of Communications on a confidential basis, that fact will be stated on the web page for such Communities.

**Retention and Security**

**Retention and Destruction of Personal Information** : It is expected that some Members will enjoy the Reachli Site and Reachli Services over a period of months or years, and it can be useful not only for Reachli but also for such Member that their personal information is to be kept on file. Reachli therefore may retain a person's Member's personal information for up to five years after their last contact with Reachli. This ensures that Reachli is able to answer questions about the Reachli Site and Reachli Services previously provided.

**Updating, Correcting, or Deleting Information:** Since Reachli uses a Member's personal information to provide him or her with access to the Reachli Site and Reachli Services, it is important that such information be accurate and complete. If any of your personal information changes or you would like to delete your account, please inform us so that we can make any necessary changes. Simply send your request via e-mail to: [team@reachli.com](mailto:team@reachli.com)

**Security of Personal Information:** Reachli takes reasonable measures to protect against loss, theft, unauthorized access, disclosure, use or modification of personal information. Such measures will vary depending on the sensitivity, amount, format, nature and storage of the personal information and will involve, as applicable, physical, organizational and electronic security measures, including premises security, restricted file access to personal information, technological safeguards including security software and firewalls to prevent unauthorized computer access, and password and security policies. Members should be aware that Reachli cannot ensure the security of personal information transmitted by regular email or across push notfications, which is not a fully secure medium.

**Changes and Questions**

**Changes to our Privacy Policy:** As part of our regular review of all of our policies and procedures, we may revise our privacy policy from time to time and may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will contact you before we use your data for these new purposes to notify you of the policy change and to provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses.

Customers may prevent their information from being used for purposes other than those for which it was originally collected by e-mailing us [privacy@reachli.com](mailto:privacy@reachli.com)

**Questions, Concerns, Requests for Access:** If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, wish to access your personal information, or wish to change your preferences regarding our use of your information, please contact us at: [privacy@reachli.com](mailto:privacy@reachli.com).

Reachli, Inc.  
Phone: (888) 600-4430  
Email: [privacy@reachli.com](mailto:privacy@reachli.com)
